Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session one of unit five it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
If you haven't already done so, you
can download and save the assessment
by clicking on the link on page four,
and then you can save the document in
a suitable location on your computer.
Once you have done that, you can then
open the assessment booklet and begin.
If you scroll down to page two, you
can pop your name at the top and
then we come to section one, which
is Understand Preventative Methods
Used to Maintain Cyber Security.
There are six learning objectives in
this session with six questions to
fulfill those learning objectives.
So the first question, in the table
below describe two routine methods
used to maintain cyber security.
So what do you do or what can be
done to maintain cyber security
... that it's common to be done?
So using your learning from
session one, think about two
methods and then describe them.
So it's a describe question, so try to
provide good detail in your response.
Then for question two, this
is an explain question.
So again you need good detail
in your response, explain what
is meant by vulnerability tests.
And so what do they do?
What is vulnerability testing?
What is its purpose?
What does it hope to achieve?
And then for question three, explain
what is meant by penetration testing.
Again, so what does
penetration testing do?
Who does that?
What is its purpose?
What will it achieve?
And then for question four, explain
what is meant by security updates.
So what are security updates?
Have you experience of
installing security updates?
What is the purpose of security updates?
Why and when should you
install security updates?
So think about what it meant, what
security updates mean, and then give
an explanation in your own words.
And then for question five, explain
what this meant by patching.
So using your learning from the
course materials, what is patching?
So we've talked about security
updates, but what exactly is patching?
How does it differ from
the security updates?
What is the purpose of patching?
Why would you need to do patching?
And then for question six, explain why
cyber security information and maintenance
records should be accurate and up to date.
So what will that achieve?
So if you maintain maintenance records
and they're accurate, they're up
to date, anything that's been done
on a computer has been logged and
could be clearly seen by anybody.
What will it achieve?
What are the benefits of that?
So once you've done that, you can then
proofread your answers and then save the
document again and move on to session two.